(Leonard:)No, no. I'm okay.
It stopped bleeding.
Anyway, you did throw up.
Isn't that a sign of a concussion?
Yes, but I get carsick too, so...
(Penny:)Okay.
(Leonard:)Sorry about your car, by the way.
(Penny:)Oh, no, it's fine.
You got most of it out the window.
(Leonard:)The poor guy on the bike.
(Leonard:)I had a nice time.
(Penny:)Yeah, me too.
Well, um, good night.
(Penny:)Good night.
(Scene:)- Leonard.
- Yeah?
(Penny:)Was this supposed to be a date?
(Leonard:)This?
(Leonard:)No.
(Leonard:)No, of course not.
(Leonard:)This was just you and me hanging out
with guys who didn't show up...
(Leonard:)...because of work and a colonoscopy.
(Penny:)Okay. I was just checking.
When I take a girl on a date...
And I do, heh.
(Leonard:)...she knows she's been dated.
Capital D. Heh.
Bold face, underlined, like, dated.
I think I might have a concussion.
I'm gonna go lay down.
(Penny:)Good night.
- So how was your date?
- Awesome. Heh.
Score one for liquor and poor judgment.